[ traffic hums ]
[ soft dramatic music ]
♪ ♪
[ engine idling ]
[ door squeaks open ]
[ door slams shut ]
[ ominous music ]
♪ ♪
- Hi .
Yes , um , I was wondering if I could get
driving directions to a nightclub called Bunker .
Yes , Bunker .
How exactly would I get there ?
[ cell phone ringing ]
- [ gasps ] It 's Amy .
- [ speaking indistinctly over phone ]
- Hello , sweetie .
- Okay .
- How are you ? We miss you so much .
- Mm-hmm .
- Yeah , we wish you were here with us .
- Mm-hmm . - Yeah .
- And , um , how - - how far away is ... this ?
- No , we 're in Germany right now .
Mm-hmm .
And then we travel to Italy in a couple of days .
- Great . Thanks .
Auf wiedersehen .
- [ laughing ] I know .
- Ooh , ooh .
Tell her we bought her a present from Holland .
- Yeah , we got you a present .
- What is it ?
- No , we can 't tell you what it is .
It 's a surprise .
- Yes .
- Oh , yes , the other thing is
that we met this cute German waiter .
Well , Jenny thinks he 's cute .
Mm-hmm .
Yeah , and he invited us to this party tonight ,
so we 're going to go .
But , uh , we should go .
So maybe we can talk to you later ?
Okay .
All right , we miss you .
- Bye , Amy . Kisses .
- Okay , bye , sweetie .
- Hmm .
I think we 're supposed to turn .
- Turn ?
I thought you knew exactly where we were going .
Do we go left or right ?
- I 'm sorry . I just don 't know where we are .
[ heavy clanging ]
What was that ?
- I have no idea .
- You - - You must have run over a pothole or something .
- We need to go out and - - and check it out .
Aw , shit .
Shit .
Shit !
Shit . Why ?
Oh , my God .
Okay , okay , um ...
Okay , we 're going to call the rental car service .
Get the papers .
- [ sighs ] Okay .
Okay .
2-1-9 ...
- Uh-huh . [ cell phone beeping ]
- 2-0-0 .
8-0-6 .
[ cell phone beeps ]
- What ?
Shit , there 's no signal .
- There 's no signal !
- There 's always a signal .
- Not out here in the middle of nowhere .
Oh , my God . Shit .
Oh .
Oh , my God .
Shit .
[ thunder rumbles ]
- Oh , my God . Oh , my God .
Let 's just get back in the car .
Okay .
Now what do we do ?
- I don 't know .
Do you know how to change a tire ?
- No , I do not know how to change a tire .
- Well , neither do I.
What are we supposed to do , just go walk
until we find a house or a person or something ?
- Lindsay , Lindsay .
I am not getting out and walking .
- Okay , so we 're just gonna sit here till the sun comes up ?
- I have heels and shorts on .
I am not going outside .
- Are those headlights ?
- Okay , roll down your window .
- What ? Are you kidding ?
I 'm not just gonna roll down the window .
- Roll down your window .
He can help .
- [ speaking German ] What 's going on , girls ?
- Hi . Yeah , um ...
we need - - we need help .
Uh , we have a flat tire .
- I know you girls .
I 've got a horny video of you at home .
- No . No , we speak English .
- Um , can you help us ?
- You 're always wet between your legs , right ?
- What is he saying ?
- I don 't know . He 's speaking German .
Um , we need - - Can you call somebody ?
- Let me get my book . Hold on .
- I 'll fuck you good and hard .
Would you like that ?
- " Ficken . " - " Ficken . "
- Look it up . - Okay , hold on .
- Hold on one second .
- Uh ...
- " Fucking . "
He said " fucking . "
- Okay , okay . Bye-bye .
- Roll your window up . - Bye .
- Would you like that ?
- Okay .
I 'm sorry .
- I told you .
Is your door locked ?
- Yes , my door is locked .
- Ew . Ew , he is so gross .
- Why is he still staring at us ?
- I don 't know . Just don 't look at him , okay ?
- I 'm not looking at him .
I just want to get out of here .
- I know . I know , I know .
Ew .
- Oh , my gosh .
- Aw .
[ engine turns over ]
Oh , my God .
Okay , we ...
we need to just - - just go .
We need to get out of here ,
and we need to walk and find someplace ,
somebody that can help us , okay ?
- Okay , but ... - We have to !
- But if we don 't find a place in , like , ten minutes ,
we are running back to this car .
- We came - - We came from over here , I swear .
- How do you know that ? All the trees look the same .
- Uh ...
- Leaving the car is the stupidest idea .
- We would have been waiting there for hours , Jenny .
- Yeah , but we could have waited ,
and it wouldn 't have been freezing cold .
- We needed to go find help , Jenny .
- Seriously ? Find help ?
How are we going to find help out here , Lindsay ?
- Well , you agreed to come along , Jenny .
This is not just my fault .
- I don 't want to stay in the car by myself .
- We just got a little lost , okay ?
- A little lost ? - Yes .
- Lindsay , we are not a little lost !
We are really lost !
You know what , Lindsay , I 'm not walking anymore .
I 'm tired of walking , okay ?
- Jenny , I 'm trying , okay ? - Trying what ?
Lindsay , we 've been out here for , like , an hour , okay ?
- Yeah , I know .
- I 'm tired , and I 'm cold .
I 'm not moving .
- I 'm not moving . - Stop it !
- No ! - Fine !
- Fine . - Fine .
- I 'm staying right here .
- Good .
Shit .
What is that ?
Oh , my God , is that - - is that a house ?
Jenny .
Jenny , look .
I think it 's a house , I swear .
It 's a - - It 's a light or something .
Come on . Let 's go .
Quick .
- Ugh , for some reason , I don 't believe you .
[ rain pattering ]
- Come on . Come on .
Oh , thank God .
Come on , okay ?
- Oh , my shoe .
Oh .
- Come on !
- Hello ? Anybody home ?
Where 's their front door ?
- It 's over here .
- Hello ?
- Lindsay . Lindsay , over here .
I found a dog .
Look .
Oh , my God . - What ?
Look at the dog cage .
- I know . - I don 't like dogs .
- I know .
- Oh , yes , yes .
Hello ? Is anyone home ?
- Hello ? Is anyone home ?
[ knocking at door ]
- I 'm ringing the doorbell . - Do you see anybody ?
- No .
Oh , wait , yes .
Hi .
- H-Hi .
- Hi .
- We got a flat tire .
Can we come in ?
- Can we use your phone
so we can call the car company service ?
- Are you alone ?
- Yes . - We 're alone .
- Come in .
[ dramatic music ]
♪ ♪
Have a seat .
[ thunder rumbles ]
You 're tourists .
- Um , we are on a road trip through Europe .
- It 's like a - -
Yeah , European vacation .
- We 're from New York .
Can you call , uh , the emergency car service
for us ?
- Are you relatives ?
- No . - No , we 're friends .
- Anyway ...
I 'll do the phone call .
- Okay , thanks .
- Something to drink ?
- Uh , water is fine .
- Yeah , just water .
[ both mouthing words ]
- [ speaking German ] Hello .
This is Dr. Heiter .
Sorry to call you so late .
But I 've got two New York girls here with car trouble .
- Well , at least he 's calling the car company for us .
- That 's just great .
Yes , thanks a lot .
Bye .
[ speaking English ] Here you go .
Water .
- Thank you .
- Water .
They 'll arrive in half an hour ...
maximum .
- You have a really lovely home .
Do you live here with your wife ?
- No .
I don 't like human beings .
- [ laughs ]
- [ speaking German ] God damn it !
Be careful , will you ? Stupid Cow .
- I 'm sorry .
- Is there something wrong with your eyes , idiot ?
[ speaking English ] I 'll get you another one .
- No , it 's okay .
I - - It 's okay .
- We can just share .
- I 'll fetch a towel .
- What just happened ?
- I don 't know .
- We need to get out of here right now .
- Okay .
- It 's freaking me out .
[ air whooshes ]
[ machinery beeps ]
[ ominous music ]
♪ ♪
- [ breathing heavily ]
- We need to just call a taxi or something
so we can go back to the hotel .
- Straight back to the hotel . Okay .
- Get the car in the morning or something .
- Okay . Yeah .
[ machinery beeps ]
I 'm really tired .
- Oh , my God .
[ clearing throat ]
[ ominous music ]
♪ ♪
Listen , um ...
if you could just call a taxi service for us ,
we 're just going to go back to the hotel .
- No .
I don 't do another phone call .
- Um , c-can I call , then ?
- No .
- I 'm tired . - What ?
- I 'm tired .
- What ?
What 's going on ? Look at me .
- The rape drug .
- Wha - - What ? - Rohypnol .
- Oh , my God . What ?
- Causes drowsiness , dizziness , disorientation ,
and memory loss .
- No .
Are you kidding ?
What are you doing to ...
Jenny .
Oh , my God . What is that ?
[ coughing ]
[ retching ]
Oh , my God .
[ coughing and moaning ]
Please .
[ panting ]
[ gasping ]
[ screaming ]
No ! No !
[ whimpering ]
No !
Aah !
[ shrieking ]
[ gasping ]
- [ sighs ]
[ birds chirping ]
- [ gasps ]
Jenny .
[ whimpers ]
- Jenny .
- [ groaning ]
- Jenny !
Jenny , wake up .
Jenny .
[ sobbing ] Oh , my God .
- Lindsay .
[ hyperventilating ]
[ shrieking ]
- Jenny .
- [ screaming and sobbing ]
Get us out of here !
[ screaming and sobbing ]
- What is going on ?
- What are you doing ?
- What is this ?
- What the fuck are you doing to us ?
What are you doing ?
- [ sobbing ] Jenny .
- Get us out of here .
[ sobbing violently ]
- My friend .
- [ grunts ]
- [ sobbing ]
- You don 't match .
- [ grunts ]
- I have to kill you .
- [ whimpering ]
[ machinery beeps ]
- Don 't take it personally .
- What is this ?
What are you doing to us ?
[ sobbing ]
What is this ?
Stop it !
[ sobbing ] Jenny .
- [ gasping ]
[ groaning ]
- [ sobbing ] Oh , my God .
Oh , my God .
[ sobs ]
[ flat beep ]
[ sobbing ]
[ shrieking ]
[ screams ]
[ birds chirping ]
[ machinery beeps ]
- [ speaking Japanese ] Who the fuck are you ?
What is this ?
Untie me , God damn it !
What are you doing ?
Untie me .
Who in the fuck are you ?
- Please .
- What are you doing ?
- [ sobbing ]
- It 's gonna be okay .
We 're gonna get out of this .
- The Japanese possess unbelievable strength
when backed into a corner .
[ yells ]
The Japanese possess incredible strength
when backed into a corner .
[ groaning ]
- I 'm Dr. Josef Heiter ,
retired but still very well known
as the leading surgeon in separating Siamese twins .
- You 're a crazy Nazi .
I 'll get you , you dirty German madman .
- Six months ago ,
I designed a never-seen operation - -
not separating anymore but creating .
I transformed my three Rottweilers
into a beautiful three-hound construction .
Good news . Your tissues match .
So ...
- [ yells ]
- I 'll explain this spectacular operation only once .
We start with cutting the ligamentum patellae ,
the ligaments of the kneecaps ,
so knee extension is no longer possible .
- [ sobbing ]
- Pulling from B and C the central incisors ,
lateral incisors , and canines
from the upper and lower jaws .
- Shut your mouth and untie me !
- The lips from B and C
and the anus of A and B are cut circular
along the border between skin and mucosa ,
the mucus cutaneous zone .
Two pedicellated grafts are prepared
and lifted from the underlying tissue .
- [ shouting ]
- V-shaped incisions below the chins of B and C
up to their cheeks ...
connecting the circular mucosa and skin parts
of anus and mouth from A to B and B to C.
Connecting the pedicellated grafts
to the chin-cheek incisions from A to B and B to C ...
- What are you babbling about ?
You really think you 'll get away with this ?
- Creating a Siamese triplet
connected via the gastric system .
Ingestion by A ,
passing through B ...
- [ retching ]
- To the excretion of C.
A human centipede ...
first sequence .
- [ sobbing ]
- [ yelling ]
- Here is your breakfast .
- [ speaking Japanese ] Hey , wait a minute .
- Propofol for the general anesthesia .
- [ stammering ]
[ squeals ]
Please stop .
- N-No !
[ sobbing ]
No !
Lindsay !
Oh .
Lindsay .
- Jenny .
- [ screaming ]
Lindsay .
[ sobbing ]
[ shrieking ]
I want my mom .
[ sobbing ]
- [ straining ]
Aah !
- [ speaking German ] Have you gone mad ?
Come here !
- No !
Oh ! No !
[ jangling ]
- Open up !
- Please !
Stop !
Why are you doing this ?
- Open up !
- You need help !
You 're a sick man !
- I 'm a sick man .
[ laughs ]
If you don 't open up immediately ,
I will ... cut your knees .
I 'll pull your teeth out one by one
without any anesthesia !
It 's your choice .
Open the door !
Open that door !
[ pounding at door ]
[ pounding stops ]
- [ gasps ]
[ sobbing ]
Stop it !
No !
Oh !
Oh , my God .
No .
[ sobbing ]
Oh . Oh !
[ shrieks ]
[ sobbing ]
No !
Uh !
[ gasps and coughs ]
Please . Please .
[ sobbing ]
Why are you doing this ?
Just let me and Jenny go , please .
We 'll give you anything ,
anything you want .
Just let us go .
- Don 't worry .
It 's only a sedation rifle .
Keep your head very still .
I don 't want to lose one of your precious eyes .
- [ gasps ]
[ dramatic music ]
♪ ♪
[ gasping ]
Just kill me !
- Ahh .
- [ sobbing ]
- One of my Rottweilers also tried to escape
just before the operation .
After I caught the dog ,
he had to take the middle position .
In this position ,
the healing pains are twice as intense .
Do you already regret your little escape ?
In fact , I 'm thankful for it ,
because now I know definitely
you are the middle piece .
- Just kill me now .
I 'd rather be dead .
- Game over .
[ equipment whirs ]
- [ sobbing ]
No !
[ rumbling ]
- Ah , shit .
The overload has cut off again .
Sorry .
[ shouting in German ]
- [ gasping ]
[ coughing ]
[ gasping ]
[ thunder rumbles ]
[ sobbing ]
[ rain patters ]
[ machinery beeps and whooshes ]
[ groans ]
[ straining ]
Ah .
[ clanging ]
[ groans ]
I 'm so sorry .
[ grunting ]
[ straining ]
Ah .
[ grunts ]
[ groaning ]
[ straining ]
[ rifle fires ]
[ gasps ]
[ whimpering ]
[ gasping ]
[ sobbing ]
Help !
[ machinery beeps ]
[ air whooshes ]
- [ grunts ]
[ straining ]
[ breathing heavily ]
[ groans ]
[ birds chirping ]
[ gasps ]
[ sighs ]
Ah .
Oh , my sweet centipede .
Oh , boy .
Looks good .
Healing well .
Ahh .
Suffering will be over soon .
You 're in a lot of pain .
I know .
Yeah .
Nice .
Okay .
Better and better .
[ whispers ] My lead .
My lead .
Hey , man .
- [ muttering ]
- Hey , man .
- [ speaking German ] Come on up .
Stand up .
You can do it .
- [ speaking English ] Yeah , yeah , come up .
Yeah , yeah .
Yeah , come .
Come up .
Up , up , up , up , up , up .
- [ groaning ]
- Yeah !
Yeah , come up here .
Come up .
Oh , yeah !
Yeah .
Yeah !
There we go !
I did it !
[ laughs ]
- Do you really think you 're God ?
[ camera clicks and whirs ]
- [ stifled moans and sobs ]
- [ sobbing and moaning ]
- [ sobbing ]
Make it all go away , please .
[ stifled sobs and moans ]
Stop this . Stop it now .
[ sobbing and moaning ]
- [ laughs ]
Yeah .
[ stifled sobs and moans ]
[ laughs ]
[ crying ]
[ stifled moans and sobs ]
[ laughing ]
[ metal clanging and clattering ]
- How dare you lock us up here ? You crazy idiot .
[ yells and growls ]
You 'll regret this , you filthy asshole .
European madman .
God damn , let us out !
[ muffled moans and sobs ]
[ sobbing and moaning continue ]
[ church bells playing light melody ]
♪ ♪
- Take The World and bring it to me .
Yeah . Good boy .
[ tapping cane ]
Come .
- [ groans ]
- [ muffled scream ]
- [ speaking German ] Bring me the newspaper .
- [ shouting ]
- Yeah .
Good boy .
Oome .
Yeah , come .
- [ muffled sobbing ]
- [ sighs ]
- [ muffled groaning ]
Then let 's walk a little bit at least .
Attention .
- What the hell are you doing ?
- [ speaking German ] One , two , three , four .
One , two , three , four .
- Just die !
- Enjoy your meal .
[ muffled sobbing ]
- That 's what you get .
I 'm not your goddamned dog .
I 'm not a dog .
[ muffled groans and sobs ]
- [ grunts ]
[ grunts ]
- [ gasps ]
[ muffled screams ]
- [ speaking English ] Do this once more again to me ,
and I 'll pull your teeth out one by one ,
you kamikaze shit hole .
- [ muffled sobbing ]
- You want to bite me ?
- [ muffled moan ]
- Now you can bite me .
Bite my boot .
Bite my boots .
Ah , Mister Kamikaze is a chicken today .
[ imitates chicken ]
[ imitating Japanese speech ]
- Do you get off on this ?
- How dare you to turn your back on me ?
I give you some educa -
[ groaning ]
- [ muffled groan ]
- [ straining ]
Shit .
I have to shit .
I 'm so sorry .
Forgive me .
- Yeah . [ laughs ]
Feed her . Feed her .
Hard !
Swallow it , bitch !
Swallow up !
- [ sobbing ]
[ squishing sound ]
- Feed her . Feed her .
Hard .
- [ muffled sobs ]
[ all whimpering ]
[ all moaning ]
- I want to sleep .
I have to sleep .
Why didn 't I cut your vocal cords ?
If you don 't shut up ...
I will catch up on it .
Doing a follow-up operation .
- [ sobbing ]
- Finally .
You want to move your ass .
That 's fine with me .
Maybe you even can escape .
Speed up . Come .
Come .
After you , please .
[ whip smacks ]
- [ screaming ]
[ whipping continues ]
[ muffled shrieks ]
- Nice and slowly !
- [ yelling ]
- [ whimpers ]
- [ coughs ]
- Strong .
Good .
- [ muffled whimpers ]
- Constipated .
Laxative .
Neostigmine . Good stuff .
- [ muffled sobbing ]
[ whimpering ]
[ muffled sobbing ]
- Jenny sector , you 're very sick .
- [ whimpering ]
- I think you 're dying .
We have to replace you .
[ intercom ringing ]
[ ringing continues ]
- Help !
- Shut up !
- [ speaking German ] Hello .
- [ speaking German ] Police . We want to talk to you .
- Just a second .
- [ muffled screaming ]
- Help !
Help us , please !
We 're in the cellar .
- Hello .
- [ speaking German ] Good day , Mr. Heiter .
Police .
This is my colleague Voller .
I 'm Detective Kranz .
May we come in a moment ?
- Of course .
Come in .
- Thank you .
- [ shouting in Japanese ]
- Take a seat .
How can I help you ?
- Sir , people are missing .
Their vehicles were found in the neighborhood .
Perhaps you could tell us more .
- I 'm afraid you 've come to the wrong house .
I 'm so busy at the moment with my research and writing
that I hardly leave the house .
Can I offer you something to drink ?
- Do you have coffee ?
- I 'm afraid I don 't have time for coffee .
I have only water .
Mr. Kranz .
- Thank you .
- Mr. Voller .
- [ shouting in Japanese ]
- [ muffled screams ]
- So tell me , what do you want to know ?
- We know you 're a first-rate surgeon ,
and we don 't want to disturb you .
But our investigation has hit a dead end .
We wouldn 't want to offend you .
- I expect you have your reasons .
I have neither the time nor the patience
for the banality of missing persons .
- What is that cage actually for ?
- Could you get to the point ?
- A witness heard an American woman
screaming on your property .
Can you explain that ?
- Absolutely not .
I have no idea what you 're talking about .
- Your silver-colored Mercedes was seen
at the place where the Dutch lorry was found .
- What do you think ?
You think there 's a connection ?
What a nerve .
Finish your drinks and get out of my house .
I have work to do .
Drink up .
Oome on . Drink up now .
Drink and hurry up a bit .
You will regret that .
I 'll see you in court ,
and you can count on being fired .
My apologies , I 'm sorry .
I 'm overworked .
I don 't get enough sleep .
I 'll just get a towel .
- Help us , then !
We 're in the cellar !
- [ muffled screaming and moaning ]
- Dear Josef , don 't stress yourself .
Everything will be okay .
[ speaking English ] I 've got two strong
and healthy replacements .
So enjoy your last moments with the Jenny tail ,
because when I 'm back , I mercy kill it .
Preparing for a new operation , a quadruplet .
See you .
- [ sobbing and moaning ]
- [ speaks Japanese ]
- [ moaning ]
- [ grunts ]
[ straining ]
- [ whistling ]
- What 's in that cellar ?
- [ speaking German ] Now you 're going too far .
What could be there ?
My laboratory , a small workroom , a torture chamber .
You 're making a fool of yourself .
- Can we take a look around ?
- No way .
My research is off-limits to you .
Do you have a search warrant ?
- I can have one in 15 minutes .
I 'll ask you again : what 's in the cellar ?
- What you 're planning is illegal , as you well know .
Shall I call the police ?
As soon as you have a warrant , you can look where you like .
- What 's this ?
- That ...
That 's insulin .
I have diabetes .
- We 'll be back in 20 minutes with a search warrant .
- If you want to waste taxpayers ' money ,
that 's your call .
- See you soon .
- [ yells ]
- [ screams ]
- [ groans ]
[ groaning ]
- [ growling ]
[ yells ]
Come on , we have to get out of here .
One , two .
Okay ?
One . Two .
One .
Two .
Come on .
One .
Two .
- [ groans ]
[ wheezes ]
One .
Two .
- [ sobs ]
- Two .
One .
Two .
- [ gasps ]
One .
- [ moaning ]
[ shrieks ]
One .
Two .
- [ sobbing ]
- One .
One .
Two .
One , two .
One ...
One .
Two .
[ shouts ]
[ shouting ]
One .
Two .
[ shouts ]
One .
Two .
Why are we in this room ?
- [ muffled grunts ]
[ excited groans ]
- Goddamn .
God !
- [ sobbing and moaning ]
- [ shouts ]
- [ muffled grunts ]
[ moans ]
- [ yelling ]
- [ whimpers ]
[ sobbing and moaning ]
- Eye for eye .
Tooth for tooth .
[ dramatic music ]
♪ ♪
- [ laughing ]
God .
Are you God ?
I 'm just a puny insect .
I cast out my parents , left my child ...
dismissed their love and led a selfish life ,
just like an insect .
No , my existence is even lower than an insect 's .
But ...
But dear God ...
That 's how I 've lived !
And this is my punishment !
I want to believe ...
that I 'm still a human being .
- [ sobbing ]
- Hey , girls .
Hey , mister .
What an insane world we live in .
[ groans ]
- No .
- [ whimpering ]
[ moans ]
- [ gurgling ]
- [ sobbing ] - [ moaning ]
[ doorbell rings ]
- [ whimpering ]
[ sobbing ]
[ whimpering ]
[ doorbell rings ]
- [ wheezing ]
[ laughs ]
- Police !
Dr. Heiter , police !
- [ laughs ]
- [ gulps ]
- Dr. Heiter .
- [ retching ]
[ retching ]
- Well , God damn it .
- [ groans ]
[ grunting ]
[ metal clanging ]
Voller !
- [ whimpering ]
[ muffled scream ]
- [ shouts ]
- Voller .
Voller !
Aah !
Ah !
[ groaning ]
[ coughing ]
[ retching ]
[ retching and groaning ]
- [ whimpering ]
- [ sobbing ]
[ both moaning and whimpering ]
- [ grunting ]
[ relieved moans ]
- [ sobbing ]
- [ whimpers ]
[ grunts ]
[ whimpers faintly ]
- [ sobbing ]
[ sobbing ]
[ whimpering ]
[ sobbing continues ]
[ violent sobbing ]
[ birds chirping ]